Oh, Yoshikage, my darling
boy, where are you?
I've looked all over and
can't find you anywhere.
You must have been forced to change
your face and name and go into hiding.
My heart aches for you, my poor son.
I'll make sure they pay dearly.
You got that?
We need to look further into
the recent missing person cases.
That includes runaways.
Hang on, didn't Kira go into hiding?
You really think he'd risk capture
by continuing his murdering spree?
He won't be able to brush
aside his murderous impulses.
That's just how serial killers work.
He will kill again.
I wonder if just waiting for something
to happen is the best way to go.
And all this time we still haven't
found a single clue leading us to Kira.
Well, it's been bothering me a lot, too.
But you guys remember what
Jotaro said, don't you?
As soon as he finds something,
we spring to action.
According to him, we should go back
to being ordinary students until then.
I'd rather hunt down that bastard Kira
than go back to hitting the books.
We almost got him before, so I
bet the next time we see him,
it'll be a one-two knockout.
Yes,
and since I'm repairing the fire damage,
I'd like to have some
renovations done, too.
That little punk!
He's snapping pictures of
people in search of my son!
Now, would you mind giving me an estimate?
Jotaro and his insufferable stand-user
posse think they're so smart!
I'll annihilate these parasites!
And the best way to do that is
by creating new stand-users!
Huh?
Wait a minute!
No doubt about it!
Altered appearance or not, the bond
of a father and son can't be broken!
I could never mistake my son for another!
I found you at last, Yoshikage!
Just you wait.
I'll find out who you
really are, imposter.
You have to be kidding me!
If that brat uncovers my son's secret,
the stand users will sniff him out.
Enough's enough.
I have to put an end to this.
I'll protect Yoshikage with
every fiber of my being.
Let the voice of love take you higher.
See ya later!
I'm going to be late, and
I'm class monitor today.
I stayed up way too late. I'm exhausted.
Man, that sucks for you.
I look like a rock, so I'm
feeling as fit as a fiddle.
Check it out, Josuke! Hmm?
Some random binoculars!
Somebody must have left them behind!
Wow, it doesn't take much to pique
your interest, does it, buddy?
Don't pick them up.
That's gross.
What? You think?
I can assure you I am not gross.
Hello, Josuke and Okuyasu.
Oh, it's you again.
Don't scare us like that, Mikitaka.
No kidding.
My heart isn't built
for that kind of shock.
Oh, you're being too kind.
That wasn't a compliment, you know.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You've got perfect timing.
It's high time for you to come
clean about something, Mr.
Alien Man.
You're not actually from
outer space, are you?
You're just a run-of-the-mill
stand-user who believes he's
an alien for some reason spell
the beans all this lion ain't cool
What do you mean?
I have no beans and I
really am an alien There
you go talking like a
freaking weirdo again,
so here's a question for you Why were you
lying out here as a pair of binoculars?
It's a little weird Well,
I wanted the two of you to see something
hence my waiting here in the open
That?
Yes.
It's a transmission tower, to be exact.
Huh, you don't say.
Eh, calling it that might be a bit of a
stretch, without any of its power lines.
It's more of a relic of the past.
When redevelopment took over here,
most of the excess power lines were
taken down and moved underground.
Why did you want us to see that old thing?
Is that what you're using to
communicate with life on other planets?
Unless I'm mistaken, there's smoke wafting
up from around the center of the tower.
Hmm?
Whoa, you're right!
Yeah, how weird.
Please use me to take a closer look.
What the?
There's a kettle! Seriously?
But how is that possible?
That tower is like 20 meters in the air!
Indeed, but aim me about
five meters higher. Huh? Huh?
You don't see that every day.
Stop hogging the alien, I wanna see!
Oh wow, it's a dude!
There's a guy sitting up
there cooking some grub!
What? Let me see.
I think that tower might be
his home, and he looks comfy?
so he's probably spent
his entire life up there.
He can fish from the river and
he's got cucumbers growing.
Nice, that's impressive.
I have to agree with you.
It's like this guy is living in one
of those fancy self-sufficient homes.
This world has no shortages
of curious individuals.
Look out!
did you see that this guy has to be a
new stand user he just flew right through
the air like it was nothing yeah i know
but what's a stand user doing living
on a transmission tower if we want to
find out the answer to that i believe
we'll need to take a closer look what do
you know they've arrived at last i wonder
what i did to finally catch their curious
eyes come on over it's been quite a
while since i've indulged in a little chit
chat check it out looks like that tower
dude might have noticed that we noticed
him you want to get closer oh yeah but
we have to play it safe we still don't I
don't know if that user is on our side,
or if he's angling to take us out.
Is there something I can do for you?
Sorry to be rude, but I'm kinda in...
This thing looks a lot bigger
once you get up close to it.
If you fellas know what's good for you,
you'll stop right there
and won't get any closer.
Didn't you two hear what I said?
Get back!
I just answered the call
of nature, and trust me,
you don't want to be
there to get the message.
I'm really not following.
What the hell?
This is disgusting!
Don't say I didn't warn you.
I needed to fertilize the garden.
That's so gross!
Watch your mouth!
That's impolite!
I designed this nifty
contraption so it would
distribute the fertilizer
to all the plants below.
I'm all about that zero-waste
lifestyle, you know.
On the right are Asiatic dayflowers,
mountain asparagus, and watercress.
They're all completely edible!
And with all of these plants around,
catching nibbling rabbits is a cinch, so
I've got the best of both worlds, baby!
No way, so you're really
living up there all alone?
Doesn't this tower belong
to some electric company?
What are you talking about?
I paid for this house with my own money.
It's all mine.
I bought this abandoned
tower for 100,000 yen and
transformed it into my
self-sufficient dream house.
You bought it?
For 100,000 yen?
Yes, that's right.
It was a steal.
Since I support myself, I'm not
stuck working for some lame company.
It's a pretty sweet life
if you think about it.
I don't have to leave the house, and I
get all the exercise I could ever need.
I mean, do you see this view?
It's spectacular.
Wait, run that by me again.
You don't even have to leave?
Just how long have you been
living up there anyway?
I suppose I've been here
for about three years now.
What?
Three years?
I probably haven't touched
terra firma in nearly a month.
What are we gonna do, Josuke?
I had no idea such an idiot was living
right under our noses in Morioh.
If you ask me, he's a pure great nutcase.
He's just living out a fantasy.
But there's no way he'd be
dumb enough to attack us.
You're right.
For now, at least, our best option is
heading back and reporting to Jotaro.
Then again, something just
doesn't feel right about this.
Hmm.
What is he doing there?
How strange.
I suppose children like to
take videos like anyone else.
But why is he hiding behind that pillar?
It's almost as if he's up
to the same thing I am.
He's following someone and
capturing their every move.
Could his target be
someone in this picture?
Hayato Kawajiri, huh?
There's something very
unusual about this kid.
Hey, I'm home! Huh?
Is that boy still here?
Hey, Josuke, it's time for school!
Haven't you left yet?
Josuke!
I could go for some food.
Hmm?
He did not.
That little shit only
thinks about himself.
He takes a giant bite out
of my favorite Comic-Core
custer and pops it back in the
fridge like it never happened?
And there were two in here.
Where's the other one?
Man, that kid pisses me off sometimes.
Hey, look sharp!
Something fell out of your pocket!
Hey, is that a photo?
Would you too mind skedaddling and -
Don't worry about picking that picture up.
I'll get it later.
It looks like an ordinary Polaroid to me.
Why is he so freaked out?
It's fine! Just leave!
What? You're...
Hey, what's going on, Josuke? That blast!
You're Kira's old man!
I should've known your crusty
ass was behind all this!
I've been waiting for this moment.
You've stepped into my abode.
If you tell someone to come in,
they chicken out and refuse,
but if you tell them the opposite,
they get pissed and enter!
You've at long last entered into
Superfly, Josuke Higashikata!
Wait, I've what?
Well done, Toyohiro Kanedaichi!
You lured him in, hook, line, and sinker!
Now our friend Josuke has a new home!
Gudos, my friend!
That sounds bad, bro!
You gotta come back!
Get moving, Josuke! No!
We finally found Kira's dad!
And he's got the arrow!
No!
Get back here!
I'm sure you're confused,
so let me explain.
Once someone steps into the tower's realm,
it won't spit them out until
its next victim steps in.
However, if they try to force their way
out, they simply become part of the tower.
That's the secret ability of my stand.
Superfly!
We've got you now, Josuke Higashikata!
Make sure he stays nice and
comfy now, Toyohiro! Ahahaha!
Kyousuke!
Damn it all!
I have a bit of a confession to make.
Superfly is indeed my stand, but
it isn't exactly under my control.
It pretty much does whatever it wants.
And now that you're here, I can take off.
I've been trapped by Superfly
for the entirety of my stay here.
Well, take care of her for me.
I've got a life to enjoy.
So,
the sly son of a bitch is in cahoots with
that grandpa ghost dude from the picture.
Mr.
Okuyasu, is there any way I could
possibly be of assistance to you?
You'll just get hurt, so stay out of it.
Your assistance is no longer needed.
Now,
if you could change your
body into some sticks
of dynamite instead of dice or binoculars,
we might have something to work with.
Oh, that would be impossible.
I can't change into any
object stronger than myself,
so explosives and large
mechanisms are off limits.
Perhaps there's another
way I can be of use.
Oh, shut up!
I already told you there's
not a damn thing you can do!
Get out of here and let
us do what we do best!
That asshole thinks I'm just gonna let
him trap his prey and make some super
cool escape But he's about to find out
he messed with the wrong stand users.
Hey, you gotta go for it Okuyasu
I'm ready to go when you are buddy.
This rusty tower has got nothing on us.
Let's bring it down Josuke
Right busting out of here is
gonna be a snap and a half
There, what are you doing?
Damn these dicks, how the
hell did they get so strong?
This thing's pretty freaking solid!
But if we keep pounding
it like we have been,
it'll snap in two and
fall over in no time.
See for yourself, you're about to come
crashing down to good old terra firma.
You dumbass, do you think
you two can scare me?
I had a feeling you'd go
straight to using your fists.
Looks like you haven't noticed yet.
This tower has absorbed the
power of your attacks and
has redistributed the force
over its entire structure!
Huh?
What's this jackass babbling about?
Hang tight!
You'll be out of this metal
death trap before you know it!
Here we go!
Hold it, Okuyasu.
Listen for a sec.
Huh?
I'm getting a real bad feeling about this.
That sound...
What the hell is he planning?
What you're hearing is the
sound of the energy left over
from your punches is reverberating
throughout the whole tower.
What?
Mind if I ask you boys a question?
Have either of you ever heard
of the law of conservation?
Once energy has been collected,
it'll eventually be released
for use in a different form?
and I wonder where it's gonna go now.
Oh shit.
Okuyasu, get down!
What?
Punch the tower as much as you'd like!
All the energy you two idiots
are putting out is just going to
go around and around and come
right back to bite you in the ass!
So go ahead!
You're only hurting yourselves!
Why not save the money and hospital
bills and accept that you're outmatched?
It doesn't matter how strong you are!
Nothing you do will be
able to destroy this tower!
Okuyasu!
I'm kinda worried, Josuke!
I wasn't quick enough to dodge it!
One of those attacks
left a hole in my sight.
Guess I should have warned
you about that, huh?
I can see your thoughts racing.
You think if you can manage to defeat
me, the user, you'll have a way out.
But that's merely a pipe dream.
Remember, this stand
exists independently of me.
Even if I were to just drop dead,
that would never stop this tower from
ensnaring victims until the end of time.
That's Superfly's special ability.
Josuke, I...
Until the end...
of time?
Don't look so serious, Josuke!
All you have to do is find
someone else to take your place!
It's not rocket science!
One person goes in and one comes out!
It's a simple exchange!
Trap some poor fool and get yourself out!
It's kinda like that card game Old Maid!
It's a lot like human society!
Just hand over the Old Maid to some
other fool and get the hell out of Dodge!
Don't you agree?
I do, wholeheartedly.
Pulling someone else in
will certainly help Josuke.
Howdy!
And I think you're the perfect candidate.
Time to go back to the tower.
You're grounded.
Holy!
Mikitaka, you sly dog!
What the hell is going on here?
Where did you come from and
how are you a power line?
What sort of power is this?
How very kind of you to ask.
I possess these powers
due to my being an alien.
Yeah, you've got him now!
Way to be useful, alien dude!
Move quickly now.
Please exit the confines of the tower, Mr.
Josuke. Damn you!
Thanks, you frickin' rock, Mikitaka!
You heard him, Josuke!
Get out of there!
Leave the tower before it's too late!
Yeah, on my way!
Sweet!
I made it out you bastard.
What even are you the guy
in the photo told me about
Josuke's allies But he never
mentioned a freak show like you
Being an alien.
I have no knowledge of this
so-called old maid game
But I don't like the way
you tricked Josuke and tried
to trap him here forever It's
an awful lot like an adult
beating a child at a New
Year's card game by cheating.
That is why I brought you back
You don't deserve to be free.
You're never leaving this tower!
Here's the thing,
I developed these really thick calluses
from swinging around up here all this time.
They're so thick, I can
hide things in them.
Now die, think head!
You seem to assume what's in
your hand is a part of me,
but I am afraid that is a misconception.
What you're holding isn't me, but the
power line you were hanging on to.
As you can see, I am fine.
Yeah he did it!
That was totally epic Mikitaka!
Now get yourself to the top and
get over here!
After years of waiting, you finally
stepped into my tower's realm.
Do you really think I'd let you walk away?
You're looking at a man who
spent every moment of every
day thinking about escaping
this godforsaken tower!
Have you already forgotten my warning?
This tower will return any attack back to
That wire is also a part of this tower.
I purposely severed the line so
that the opening would face you.
Is this really the place
where I meet my end?
No! Mikitaka!
Get your ass out of there!
I can heal the wound, but
you have to leave the tower!
Oh, no!
The only one leaving here is me!
Direction and angle check.
If you strike it, it strikes back.
Mikitaka!
You sick bastard!
You definitely made escaping a
little bit tougher, I must admit,
but all of that ugliness is behind us now.
I would wager prying those suckers
out will sting just a touch,
but you'll have all the
time in the world to heal.
Feel free to use the
medicinal herbs in the garden.
Bastard!
I'll make sure you pay for that!
Even if you somehow manage
to make it out of that tower,
I'll chase your deceitful
ass to the ends of the earth!
Oh, you can try, but you won't succeed.
From what that old man told me,
you still haven't even uncovered
the whereabouts of Yoshikage Kira.
Kira!
Who is this?
I've never seen him before.
They have to figure out who that man is.
I don't need to try to
explain it as old, I'm tired.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly.
To the arms and the lips and the face.
So the human can have all
that I need to, I want to.
Come and stand a little bit closer.
Breathe in and get a bit higher.
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you?
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you.
Ooh, I gotta find help.
Ooh, I want you, I don't know?
If I need you, but I do,
but I'm trying to find you.